gamesxl.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy - Games XL .com

Gamesxl.com (hereinafter: Website) respects the privacy of all users of its site and ensures that the personal information you provide to us is treated as confidential. Personal information is processed and protected by us with due care. In this respect we comply with the requirements of the Dutch Telecommunications Act and the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act.

You should realize that other interests, such as the investigation into illegal activities, may in some cases prevail over your right to privacy.

Admeen B.V. is responsible for the processing of the data on Website. In this privacy statement, we explain which personal data we collect and use, and for what purpose. Because our processing falls within the statutory exemption schemes, it has not been reported to the Dutch Data Protection Authority.

Attention! **If you're not 16 yet** , you should first ask your parents or legal representative (hereinafter: Parents) for permission for providing your personal data and for using our Website!

  1. ## Summary processing personal data

Stated below are the main reasons and personal data we, and our third party partners, process (mainly through cookies).

Processing purpose | Data | Party storing or reading the data | Privacy statement  
---|---|---|---  
Making sure the website functions as it should function. | Recently played-, saved-, and reported games and your progress in particular games;  
Browser techniques (to be able to play games);  
Profile status, if you have a profile we can see if you are logged in or not;  
Specific settings you apply, for example a theme on our Website or the position of the mobile menu button. | Website | This privacy statement.  
Analyze user statistics and behavior to become aware of the popularity the performance and to improve Website (experience) and our services. | IP address to count unique users;  
Browser information;  
The Operation System (Windows for example);  
Time and duration of visit;  
Which pages are visited on our Website; | Google Analytics | [link](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en "Google Analytics Privacy Policy")  
  
By offering advertisements on Website that generate income for Website, we are able to offer the games on Website free of charge. We integrate advertising data with Google Analytics (as described above). With the advertising features of Google Analytics implemented we are able to use:

    * Remarketing with Google Analytics
    * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
    * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
    * Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data via advertising cookies and identifiers

By doing so, advertisements are more attractive for you as user and we are able to improve our campaigns for instance to make sure you're not seeing the same advertisement twice.

If you click on our advertisement on a website, we are able to adjust the content of Website to make sure the Website contains the content of the advertisement (that particular popular game for example)

Google is using these cookies for advertisements displayed on the internet and on other Google services, such as YouTube, to show advertisements that match your interests.

| The types of cookies used by Google are explained on: [www.google.com/policies/technologies/types/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/types/ "Types of cookies used by Google")

If you wish to opt-out: [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ "Google Analytics opt-out")

| Google | [link](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/ "Google Partners Privacy Policy")  
Log in with your Facebook account on Website;  
To facilitate a Like on Facebook if you push the LIKE button and to monitor your visit to our Website.  
When logged in on Facebook and visiting Website, Facebook knows you've visited Website. Facebook keeps records of every website that displays the LIKE button. | For this information we refer to the privacy statement of Facebook. | Facebook | [link](https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy "Facebook Privacy Policy")  
Log in with your Google account on Website;  
To facilitate a +1 on Google+ if you push the G+1 button. | For this information we refer to the privacy statement of Google. | Google | [link](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/policies/privacy/ "Google Privacy Policy")  
Log in with your Twitter account on Website. | For this information we refer to the privacy statement of Twitter. | Twitter | [link](https://twitter.com/privacy "Twitter Privacy Policy")  
To make sure you can logon and we are able to recognize you for instance for your high scores, recently played games, favorites and Website preferences;  
Keeping record of game rankings. | Your username and e-mail;  
Day of birth;  
IP address;  
Registration and login date;  
If you have provided these: your first and last name;  
The same data as stated under 'Making sure the website functions as it should function'. | Website  
We are saving this in our database (this information is not stored in a cookie). | This privacy statement.  
Assuring that the games of our partner function as they should. It seems you're playing a game on our Website, but it is loaded from a partner website. Think of the game as a painting that is hosted elsewhere, while you see it through our Website that functions as the frame for the painting. They are given space on our Website to make it possible for you to play their game. It is up to the third party to inform you about their processing activities. That's the reason you might bump into another cookie bar. | As explained we don't exactly know which personal data third parties are processing. Nevertheless we've displayed our most important partners and their privacy statements at the right, to make sure you are informed about their processing activities. | CoolGames  
Famobi  
OrangeGames  
Poki | [link](http://www.coolgames.com/en/static/privacy-policy "CoolGames Privacy Policy")  
  
  2. ## Recording and processing of data

By using the Website you leave behind certain personal information. In this respect a distinction can be made between (personal) data provided actively and (personal) data provided passively. Personal data provided actively are the data that you have filled in yourself on the Website. For instance, your name, email address, that you are asked to fill in when registering on the site for creating a profile. Data provided passively are the data that are stored automatically during your surfing on the Website. For instance, the IP address and the operating system of your computer, and the browser you are using. If you are logged in to the Website as a User, both actively and passively provided personal data will be stored. If you are not logged in, only passively provided personal data will be stored.

We will not make available the personal data linked to your profile to third parties unless we are legally obliged to do so or you have given your explicit permission to do so.  
In the case of (suspected) fraud or abuse of our Website, we may hand over personal data to the competent authorities. Also in the event that the Website is taken over by another owner it will be necessary to provide all data to that new owner. We do work with partners which fill parts of our Website. Think of the game as a painting that is hosted elsewhere, while you see it through our Website that functions as the frame for the painting. They are given space on our Website to make it possible for you to play their game. We are not responsible for the processing activities of these third parties.

  3. ## Parents and Children

Are you younger than 16? If so, you should ask your parents for permission for entering your personal information.

Are you the father, mother or legal representative of a child playing games on our website and do you wish to withdraw your permission? You can do so at any time. In order to cancel an account / a profile please contact us by means of the contact form on the Website. We may ask you to identify yourself to make sure the profile is that of your child. We would not want to delete a profile belonging to somebody else.

  4. ## Data provided actively

    1. ### Registration

To be able to create a profile, registration is required. We store the personal information entered by you, such as your email address and day of birth.

    2. ### Profile

In your profile you have access to the personal data that you have provided to us and you can change this information if necessary. Your profile is only accessible with your username and password. To prevent abuse it is not allowed to make the password available to third parties.

    3. ### Contact form

If you complete a contact or application form on the website, of if you send us an email message, the data that you send to us will be stored for as long as required for a full reply to, and handling of, the form or message, in accordance with the nature of the form or the content of your email message.

    4. ### Username and password

Your username is associated with a password. You yourself are responsible for handling your password with due care. We assume that a person who logs in with your username and password is authorized to use your profile. If you suspect that the password is known to unauthorized persons, you must contact us as soon as possible, so we can take measures.

    5. ### Storage term

We will keep the data provided by you to us actively for as long as your profile is in use or until you indicate that you want to delete the profile. If you delete your profile, Website will keep your profile information for an additional period of 30 days in case you come to regret the deletion or in case there are complaints about material / information posted by you after you have deleted your profile.

In case of abuse of the Website and a subsequent deletion, we will keep your profile information to prevent abuse in the future.

In case a profile is not accessed for 2 years, we will mark the profile as inactive and remove all the profile information belonging to this profile.

  5. ## Data provided passively

    1. ### Click behaviour and visitor data

On Website, general visitor information is stored for statistical analysis with respect to the Website. General visitor information is deemed to include your IP address, the time of the visit and data sent along by a visitor's browser.

    2. ### Use of cookies

Website uses cookies. A cookie is a simple small file that is sent along with pages of this Website and that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard disk. It is possible to disable cookies, but we advise against this strongly. For turning off the cookies will limit the functionality of the Website considerably. If, after the cookie bar is shown, you decide to click on Website you consent with Website storing cookies. If you have a profile, than Website, after logging in with your username and password, will automatically place a cookie on your computer in order to be able to recognize you during the remainder of a session. The information that is obtained by us in this way will be used by us to optimize our Website according to your wishes and preferences.

Cookies make the website much easier and more personal. There are different types of cookies.

      1. #### Necessary:

These cookies are enabled to view Website and to use the basic functions, like the automatic login. These cookies are automatically stored without consent needed.

      2. #### Functional:

These cookies make it possible for you to save your preferred setting, like your favorite color and your avatar.

      3. #### Presentation:

Because of these cookies we can show you which games you have played, which games you have marked as favorite and remember which games you have reported. These cookies are automatically stored without consent needed.

      4. #### Third-party:

Because of these cookies we can display advertisements tuned to your interests.

These cookies are stored after your consent. You do so by pressing "I agree" in the cookie bar or if you decide to click on the Website after the cookie bar has popped up.

**Deleting cookies**

Got objections against cookies? If you want to delete cookies, you should do this in the settings of your browser. We can not help you do this, because the cookies are stored in your browser. Consult the "help" function of your browser if needed. On [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/ "Your Online Choices") third party cookies can be deleted in such a manner that these cookies are not restored on other websites.

    3. ### Google

Our website contains advertisements that are supplied by the U.S. company Google. Use may be made of cookies and other technologies, such as Google Analytics, to track how Users use the Website. The information thus obtained, including the address of your computer (IP address), will be transmitted to, and stored by, Google on servers in the United States.

Google uses this information to track how our Website is used, to report to us about the Website and to be able to offer its advertisers information about the effectiveness of their campaigns. Google may make available this information to third parties if Google is legally required to do so, or in as far as such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. This is beyond our control.

The following Google Analytics advertising features are implemented on Website:

      * Remarketing with Google Analytics
      * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
      * Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting
      * Integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data via advertising cookies and identifiers

You can opt-out for Google Analytics advertising features with the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ "Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on") or through '[Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads "Google Ad Settings")'.

    4. ### Other external advertising companies

We also use other external advertising companies to display ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to display advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you want more information or if you want to prevent that these companies use this information, please click on [this link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ "Consumer Opt-out - Network Advertising Initiative").

    5. ### Storage term

We will not store data provided passively longer than strictly necessary for the purpose for which they were collected.

  6. ## Third party websites

This statement does not apply to third party websites linked to this Website through links. We can not guarantee that third parties will handle your personal data in a reliable or secure way. We recommend that you should read the privacy statements of the third party websites, before entering your personal information there.

  7. ## Amendments to privacy statement

Website may amend this statement. It is therefore recommended to read this statement regularly, so that you will be aware of these changes.

  8. ## Access and amendments to personal data

You may amend and/or delete your personal data provided actively on your profile page.

You may at all times communicate all your questions about our privacy policy or questions regarding access and amendments to (or removal of) your personal data to Website. You are requested to use our [contact form](http://admeen.com/contact/?ref=http://www.gamesxl.com "Contact form") for that purpose.

**Admeen B.V.**  
Attn Gamesxl.com  
Hanzeplein 11-27  
8017 JD Zwolle  
the Netherlands 

E-mail: legal@admeen.com

We have been registered with the Chamber of Commerce under number: 08154287
